Abdallah Bahaa

King Faisal Street, Giza (+20) 1203588860 abdallah.bahaa2000@gmail.com Linkedin

SUMMARY

Computer science fresh graduate with a major in mobile and cloud computing. Experienced in Android mobile development. proficiency in Java, Kotlin, and Python, and certifications in mobile development and UI/UX design. possess strong problem-solving skills and experience working with cross-functional teams. Highly motivated and committed to continuous learning and growth.

EDUCATION

Canadian International College, New Cairo — Bachelor of Computer Science Mobile and Cloud Computing Major **(2019-2023)** GPA: 3.53

EXPERIENCE

Ministry of Communication and Information Technology(MCIT) -

July 2022 - Aug. 2022

Training in Infrastructure, wireless and voice, Datacenter, Cybersecurity, Data science

Artronix Company - Mobile Developer Trainee

July 2021 - Aug. 2021

Android development training by building various projects, by java and kotlin

COURSES

Advanced Android Kotlin - Fwd & Udacity (Certificate)

User Interface and User Experience – Information Technology Institute (Certificate)

Machine Learning - CIC Faculty of Engineering (Certificate)

Python Programming - CIC (<u>Certificate</u>)

Web Design - CIC (Certificate)

Data Analysis With Python - CIC (Certificate)

MILITARY SERVICE: COMPLETED

Oct. 2023 - Dec, 2024

SKILLS

Hard Skills:

- Android Mobile Development
- Machine learning
- Iava
- Kotlin
- Python
- C++
- Flask
- Laravel
- Microsoft Power Bi

Soft Skills:

- Leadership Experience
- Presentation
- Communication
- Team work
- Project management

PROJECT

• Editor at imas2023 website

GRADUATION PROJECT

- **Project name:** Smart E-learning application
- Project description: Smart e-learning platform that connects students and companies through intelligent tools such as a recommendation system, content creation tools, and a CV creator.
- Grade: A+

LANGUAGES

- Native Arabic Speaker
- Advanced English